GORDON ZHONG

(720)-579-1587

✓ GordonZhongCodes@gmail.com

Las Vegas, NV 89118



https://zhong.ventures

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ gordon-zhong/

PROFILE SUMMARY

Passionate young professional with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, three years of experience as a Software Engineer, and a Master of Business Administration. Grew up actively involved in and contributed heavily to my family's small Chinese restaurant, which instilled a deep appreciation for face-to-face interactions and providing exceptional customer service. Currently looking for a stable management position to learn more about the food & beverage sector and to gain experience with franchising operations, as well as the service & hospitality industry.

EDUCATION

2023 - 2024 U. OF NORTHERN COLORADO

- Master of Business Administration
- GPA: 3.94 / 4.00

2016 - 2020

- B.S. Computer Science
- Major GPA: 3.8 / 4.0
- Cumulative GPA: 3.7 / 4.0

U. OF COLORADO, DENVER

- SKILLS + CERTS.
- Microsoft Office Specialist
- Food Handler Card
- 140 WPM Keyboard
- Efficient Time Management
- Excellent Verbal & Written Communication
- Positive Mentality
- Team-Oriented

LANGUAGES

- English: Fluent, Native Language
- Cantonese: Conversational
- Technical: Typescript, HTML, SQL, C#, Angular, React, TailwindCSS, Python, ASP.NET Core

WORK EXPERIENCE

7Leaves Cafe - Las Vegas, Nevada

2024 - PRESENT

Team Member

- · Delivering exceptional customer service while ensuring a positive and welcoming atmosphere for all guests.
- · Following company policies and procedures, including equipment handling and safety guidelines.
- Preparing high-quality beverages and products in line with company recipes, ensuring consistency and meeting customer preferences.
- · Communicating effectively with team members and management to support smooth operations.

S&P Global - Englewood, CO

2020 - 2023

Associate I Software Engineer

- Promoted from Associate SWE to Associate I SWE within 6 months
- Full-stack engineer on the Energy studio project, a GIS-based web application for building and storing interactive queries, allowing users to filter and drill down on energy and oil data.
- · Pioneer in the Bricks Design System, a library of reusable front-end Angular components to be shared by applications across the entire company Energy division.

Health Data Compass - Denver, CO

2019 - 2020

Data Engineer Intern

- · Tested, documented, and presented enterprise web APIs for future company use.
- Explored and implemented applications on Google Cloud Platform for use in production.
- Developed Python scripts to assist and automate current manual processes.
- Followed HIPAA security constraints and conduct in all the work completed.